Guide to the K.C Parsons publications collection, 1915-1999
Parsons, K.C. publications, 1915-1999
- Series: Western US
  - Environmental goals for the Los Angeles region, July 1967 (Box 5)
    Created by Environmental Goals Committee, Los Angeles Region Goals Project
  - General plan: Los Altos, California, planning area, August 1954 (Box 5)
    Created by Los Altos City Planning Commission
  - City of Santa Monica: land use and circulation elements, final elements intended for adoption by the city council, September 1984 (Box 5)
    Created by Santa Monica Planning Commission
  - City of Santa Monica: land use and circulation elements, final draft, 1984 (Box 5)
  - Western Addition District redevelopment study, November 1947 (Box 5)
  - Master plan: City of Los Angeles. 2.0: Public service plans, 1969 (Box 5)
    Created by Los Angeles Department of City Planning
    Binder of fold-out poster maps
  - Land use and issues in Orange County 1968 (Box 5)
    Created by Orange County Planning Department
    Large foldout poster; received as mailing
  - San Jose, CA. The general plan: 1966-2010, June 1966 (Box 5)
    Created by San Jose City Planning Department
  - The service-systems element and related portions of the Los Angeles city general plan: staff working paper, September 1969 (Box 5)
    Created by Advance Planning Division, Los Angeles Department of City Planning
  - Policy for planning: Santa Clara County, California, July 1965 (Box 5)
    Created by County of Santa Clara Planning Department
  - Architectural advisory panel evaluation report: Redevelopment of the Golden Gateway, August 1960 (Box 5)
    Created by San Francisco Redevelopment Agency
    Collection of redevelopment proposals by various architect/developer teams
  - Architectural advisory panel evaluation report: Diamond Heights/Red Rock Hill competition, June 1961 (Box 5)
  - Architectural program statement: Diamond Heights/Red Rock Hill competition, February 1961 (Box 5)
    Rules and regulations for competition
  - The Headwaters Forest stewardship plan: a citizens' alternative to Maxxam management of Headwaters Forest, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    Created by Trees Foundation
    Xeroxed copy of part of Plan for Public Comment
  - San Francisco civic center development plan: preliminary report, July 1957 (Box 5)
    Created by Architects and Engineers for San Francisco Civic Center Development Plan
  - Design and physical development plan, volume 1: Culver City, CA, April 1974 (Box 5)
    Created by Urban Innovations Group
  - Tia Juana River Valley Plan: San Diego, California, March 1977 (Box 5)
    Created by San Diego City Planning Commission
  - Alternative futures: trends and choices. Executive summary, October 1990 (Box 5)
    Created by County of Santa Clara Strategic Vision Steering Committee
  - Site feasibility study for San Francisco John Hancock Mutual Life Insurance Company (Box 5)
    Created by Skidmore Owings & Merrill
  - Vision for change: strategies for meeting Santa Clara County's workforce, family and community needs in the 21st century, June 1993 (Box 5)
  - CPO Regional Transportation Plan, September 1976 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    Created by San Diego Region's Council of Governments Comprehensive Planning Organization
  - San Diego Region's Council of Governments (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Plan analysis sessions: San Francisco, CA ULI 1978 fall meeting (Box 5, Folder 2)
    Materials for plan analysis workshop sessions at ULI meeting
  - Map of Greater San Francisco Bay Area (Box 5, Folder 2)
    Created by Rand McNally & Company
    Map has various "tour" routes; also has KC Parsons' handwritten notes
  - The San Diego general plan study, December 1961 (Box 8)
    Created by San Diego City Planning Department
  - The Golden Gateway: a proposal to the Redevelopment Agency for the development of the public garage and residential areas of Project Area E-1 in San Francisco submitted by Golden Gateway Center, 1960 (Box 8)
    Created by Golden Gateway Center
  - San Francisco civic center development plan. Space requirements: city and county courts and offices, May 1957 (Box 8)
    Created by Wurster, Bernardi and Emmons et al.
  - State development strategies: proceedings of a seminar co-sponsored by the Council of State Planning Agencies and the American Institute of Planners State Planning Committee, August 1966 (Box 8)
    Created by U.S. Department of Commerce Economic Development Administration, Office of Regional Development Planning
    Seminar held in Portland, OR, August 13-14, 1966
  - Master plan: Corvallis, OR, 1945 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    Created by Arthur D. McVoy
  - Grand Valley, Colorado: a plan for the development of the Grand Valley of the Colorado River, 1958 (Box 8)
    Created by Department of City and Regional Planning, Cornell University
    Graduate student report
  - Newman: draft general plan (map), September 1991 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    Draft general plan map: CA?